<DataSet><Query><Title>Latest Instance For Financial Period - Annual Net EPS - Diluted value</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Basic%20CIQ%20financials%20query.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample query below retrieves Latest Instance For Financial Period Annual Net EPS - Diluted value for International Business Machines Corporation (112350).</Description></Query><Query><Title>View basic balance sheet items</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/BasicBalanceSheetItems.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Security, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query displays basic balance sheet items for a single company for  the most recent four quarterly periods.</Description></Query><Query><Title>View basic income statement items</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/BasicIncomeStatementItems.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Security, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query displays basic income statement items for a single company as  of a specific period end date for original and all restatement filings.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Build a time series</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/BuildTimeSeries.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Security, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample query below retrieves one data item, quarterly total revenue,  for Abbott Laboratories (Ticker ABT) that will be presented in a time series.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Build a time series using filing dates</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/BuildTimeSeriesUsingFilingDate.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Security, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following example demonstrates how to build a time series using filing dates. The sample  query below retrieves one data item, quarterly cost of goods sold, for Anadarko Petroleum  Corp (GVKEY 011923) that will be presented in a time series.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Retrieves a specific company Business Segment Revenue as per Period End Date</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/CIQ%20Premium%20Financials%20-%20Segment%20-%20Attempt%20to%20match%20platform.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Company, Document Reference, Finl Premium Core, Finl Premium Segment Financials, Finl Premium Segment Profiles</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample query below retrieves a specific company Business Segment Revenue as per Period End Date, primary NAIC classification and primary SIC classification.</Description></Query><Query><Title>CIQ Premium Financials PIVOT</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/CIQPremiumFinancialsPIVOT.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Foundation Company , CIQ Premium Financials Core, CIQ Premium Financials Detail, CIQ Base Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>PIVOT's Premium Financials for a few specific items for a set CompanyID ", for a set Calendar Year. LatestPeriodFinancialFlag=1</Description></Query><Query><Title>Moving Averages in CIQ Price Equity for company Andeavor Logistics LP</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Calculating%20Moving%20Averages%20in%20CIQ%20Price%20Equity%20(50-Day%2C%20100-Day%2C%20200-Day).sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Company, Base Exchange Rates, Market Capitalization, Prices Intraday 1990s, Base Security</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10, 17</DataSet><Description>The following sample query below Calculating Moving Averages in CIQ Price Equity for company Andeavor Logistics LP (Tradingitemid - 119026799).</Description></Query><Query><Title>Number of quarterly instances by region using Dynamic Pivot</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/CountOfInstancesByRegion.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Foundation Company Daily, Finl Premium Core</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample query below retrieves count the number of quarterly instances by Region using Dynamic Pivot.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Display the order of items in a financial statement</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/DisplayOrderOfItemsInFinancialStatement.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Premium Financials Segment Financials, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query displays the order of Items in an Income Statement. The  description corresponding to the reportingTemplateId is provided within the query.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Latest Financials Coverage</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Financials%20Query.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Data Item Master, Finl Premium Capital Structure, Finl Premium Detail, Finl Premium Market, Finl Premium Ratio, Finl Premium Statement, Finl Premium Supplemental, Finl Premium Core</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>Extract the top 500 companies related annual financials data considering  filing date on or before inputted date and considering the latest filings  for each financial instance.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Identify Premium Financial data items</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Identify%20Premium%20Financial%20data%20items.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Packages Required, CIQ DataItem Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query displays data items associated with each Premium Financials Package.  The dataItemGroupId corresponding to each package is listed in the where clause.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Groups COUNT's of CompanyID's within CIQ Latest Financials with non-Null revenue for each Calendar Year broken into Bands</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Latest%20Financials%20Coverage%20-%20Annual%20Total%20Revenue%20in%20Bands.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Financials Latest Intraday Ratio, Premium Financials Detail, Finl Latest Ratio, Finl Latest Supplemental, Finl Latest Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Exchange Rates</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample query below retrieves Groups COUNT's of CompanyID's within CIQ Latest Financials ", with non-Null revenue for each Calendar Year broken into Bands of  less than 10 Mil, between 10 and 50 Mil and greater than 50 Mil This converts Total Revenue to USD before adding to Bands</Description></Query><Query><Title>Latest Annual Filing for Latest Period</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/LatestAnnualFilingForLatestPeriod.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core package , Premium Financials Statement package, Premium Financials Core package PLUS Premium Financials Statement package, Company, Data Item Master, Currency and Exchange</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL queries display latest Annual Filing for a company for current period.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Universe of companies determines the most recent annual filing as of the observation date</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Most%20Recent%20Annual%20Data%20Given%20An%20Observation%20Date%20(1).sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Company, Base Data Item Master, Finl Premium Core, Financials Premium Intraday Detail, Financials Premium Intraday Market, Finl Premium Detail, Finl Premium Market, Finl Premium Ratio, Finl Premium Statement, Finl Latest Core</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>This query takes an observation date, and then for a universe of companies determines the most recent annual filing as of the observation date. Query can be customized for other period types and data items.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Display multiple instances for one period</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/MultipleInstancesForOnePeriod.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL queries display multiple instances for one period for a single company.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Display multiple instances for one period</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/MultipleInstancesForOnePeriod_2.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, CIQ Data Item Master, Base Security</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The latestFilingForInstanceFlag is used when there are multiple records in the ciqFinInstance  table that have the same financialPeriodId and the same filingDate.This would occur, for  example, when a company filed its press release and its 10-Q on the same day. The  latestFilingForInstanceFlag flag shows you the \xe2\x80\x9cbest\xe2\x80\x9d instance to use if you are trying to  select between these two instances. A flag indicating that this instance is the latest one  for the financial period. If there are multiple instances, 1=the latest filing that exists for  the financial period and 0= other instances. instanceTypeId=4 (Backward column of a press  release) are excluded from consideration if instanceTypeIds of 2 or 3 exist (Original Instance  or Encore) for that financial period, as this would be replacing a complete source (e.g., an  SEC filing) with an incomplete source (e.g., a press release), To view the latestbest source  for a company, always screen for latestForFinancialPeriodFlag=1.</Description></Query><Query><Title>View the original filings for a single data item</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/OriginalFilingsForSingleDataItem.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query displays the original filings for a single data item  for a given company</Description></Query><Query><Title>Point-in-time sample query which calculates the average lag for US companies</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/PointInTimeCalculateAverageEntryLag.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Company, Base Foundation Company Daily, Financials Premium Intraday Core, Finl Latest Core, Finl Premium Core</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query uses the Premium Financials Instance Date package to calculate the average lag for US companies, based on the restatement and form types. The query limits  the universe to US, Original 10-Q collection for post 2009 records.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Point-in-time date progress showing quarterly records</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/PointInTimeDateProgressShowingQuarterlyRecords.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Company, Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Instance Date</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query uses the Premium Financials Instance Date package to display Apple's filing vs. point-in-time date progression."]</Description></Query><Query><Title>Latest Financials Coverage</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Pulling%20US%20Primary%20Listed%20IPO's%20for%20given%20YEAR%20range%20and%20then%20pulling%20Fundamentals%20for%20those%20based%20on%20another%20YEAR%20range..sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Security, Base Company, Transactions Offering, Primary GICS, Document Reference, Base Exchange Rates, Base Data Item Master, Finl Premium Capital Structure, Finl Premium Detail, Finl Premium Market, Finl Premium Ratio, Finl Premium Statement, Finl Premium Supplemental, Financials Premium Intraday Core</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10, 44</DataSet><Description>Pulling US Primary Listed IPO's from Transactions for given YEAR range and then pulling Fundamentals for those based on another YEAR range.", Can set Fundamentals Range - Default is 3 Years pre-IPO and 3 Years Post-IPO. Also running a REPLACE on DataItemName to switch commas with hyphens for CSV exporting. Built for The Capital Group to replace a CIQ screenexcel sequence</Description></Query><Query><Title>Display reported currency and convert to target currency</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/ReportedCurrencyAndConvertToTargetCurrency.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Security, Base Exchange Rate V2, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL queries display the currency in which financials were reported  and convert the data to a target currency.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Retrieve company information by a different identifier</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/RetrieveCompanyInformationWithGVKEY.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Financials Premium Intraday Core, Base Foundation Company, GVKey Enhanced</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query demonstrates how to use the ciqSymbol table to retrieve company  information by a different identifier. The sample query below retrieves company  information for Sony Corporation (GVKEY 009818).</Description></Query><Query><Title>Retrieve GICS classifications for segments</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/RetrieveGICSClassificationsForSegments.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Segment Profiles, Intel Key Documents, Base Foundation Company, CIQ Primary GICS</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query demonstrates how to provide the GICS classifications for  each segment associated to a filing date. The sample query below retrieves company information  for International Business Machines (companyId 112350). Note: This query uses the GICS package (in the SymbolHelper files) and the S and P Capital IQ  Key Documents package</Description></Query><Query><Title>Identify same-day updates for income statement data</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/SameDayIncomeStatementItems.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query pulls all S and P Capital IQ same day income statement  data for the first quarter of 2012</Description></Query><Query><Title>Pulls from and thru dates for each fiscalChainSeriesId change, including when the Id changes back to a previous fiscalChainSeriesId (i.e., Morgan Stanley 472898)</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/Sequential%20FiscalChainSeriesId%20-%20CIQ.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Data Item Master, Finl Premium Core, Finl Premium Detail, Finl Premium Market, Finl Premium Ratio, Financials Premium Intraday Core</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample query below retrieves Pulls from and thru dates for each fiscalChainSeriesId change,  including when the Id changes back to a previous fiscalChainSeriesId (i.e., Morgan Stanley 472898). Notes - --Identify single fiscalChainSeriesId for fiscal year for smooth time series (eliminates overlapping data but may result in overlapping periods included in each fiscal year) --The query only selects the max fiscal period data for any given document so restatements will not be included in the fiscalChain selection --FiscalYear in the Quarterly table is just the year of the periodEndDate so might not perfectly aline with all companies - FYI</Description></Query><Query><Title>TEV/EBITDA time series</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/TEV_EBITDA_TimeSeries.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>CIQ Premium Financials Core, CIQ Premium Financials Detail, Market Capitalization</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>Calculates a quarterly time series of TEVEBITDA by joining pricing  date to period end date</Description></Query><Query><Title>View a time series for a single data item</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/TimeSeriesForSingleDataItem.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query displays a time series for a single data item for a company.</Description></Query><Query><Title>Total Company Shares Outstanding on a specific date</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/TotalCompanySharesOutstandingOnDate.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Base Security, Prices Intraday Recent History or other CIQ Market Data , CIQ Financials Capital Structure Equity</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10, 17</DataSet><Description>Calculate company-level, aggregated shares outstanding on a particular  historical date, incorporating both traded and non-traded shares  outstanding and any relevant conversion factors.</Description></Query><Query><Title>View as-reported details for a company\xe2\x80\x99s debt capital structure</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/ViewAsReportedDetailsCapitalStructure.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Premium Financials Capital Structure, Base Foundation Company, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query demonstrates how to view as reported details for IBMs  FY 2009 debt capital structure. Note: This query is for the Debt Capital Structure Add-On delivered via a separate package.</Description></Query><Query><Title>View all business segment financials for a company</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/ViewBusinessSegmentFinancials.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Premium Financials Segment Financials, Base Foundation Company, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query demonstrates how to view the latest annual business segment  financials for International Business Machines Corp. (in the reported currency). Note: This sample query includes data from all Segment Add-On packages: the Segment Financial  Data Add-On package (loads into ciqFinCollectionData table), the Segment Financials Add-On,  and the Segment Profiles Add-On.</Description></Query><Query><Title>View summary debt information for a company</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/ViewCompanySummaryDebt.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Premium Financials Capital Structure, Base Foundation Company, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query demonstrates how to view summary debt information for IBM over a 10-year period. Note: This sample query is for the Capital Structure Add-On delivered through the  ciqFinCollectionData table in the Premium Financials Core Package.</Description></Query><Query><Title>View the sources, values and filing dates</Title><WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/MSSQL/ViewSourcesValuesAndFilingDates.sql</WebSiteUrl><ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Security, Data Item Master</ReqPackage><DatabaseType>MSSQL</DatabaseType><QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion><QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate><DataSet>10</DataSet><Description>The following sample SQL query displays the sources, values and filing dates for a specific  company and data item as of a specific period end date.</Description></Query><Query>
  <Title>Latest Instance For Financial Period - Annual Net EPS - Diluted value</Title>
  <WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/Oracle/BASIC%20Latest%20Annual%20Filing%20for%20Latest%20Period.sql</WebSiteUrl>
  <ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Data Item Master</ReqPackage>
  <DatabaseType>ORACLE</DatabaseType>
  <QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion>
  <QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate>
  <DataSet>10</DataSet>
  <Description>The following sample query below retrieves Latest Instance For Financial Period Annual Net EPS - Diluted value for International Business Machines Corporation (112350).</Description>
</Query>
<Query>
  <Title>Identify Premium Financial data items</Title>
  <WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/Oracle/Identify%20Premium%20Financial%20data%20items.sql</WebSiteUrl>
  <ReqPackage>Packages Required, CIQ DataItem Master</ReqPackage>
  <DatabaseType>ORACLE</DatabaseType>
  <QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion>
  <QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate>
  <DataSet>10</DataSet>
  <Description>The following sample SQL query displays data items associated with each Premium Financials Package.  The dataItemGroupId corresponding to each package is listed in the where clause.</Description>
</Query>
<Query>
  <Title>View the sources, values and filing dates</Title>
  <WebSiteUrl>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/SP-Global-Xpressfeed/CIQPremiumFinancials/master/Oracle/ViewSourcesValuesAndFilingDates.sql</WebSiteUrl>
  <ReqPackage>Premium Financials Core , Premium Financials Detail, Premium Financials Statement, Base Foundation Company, Base Security, Data Item Master</ReqPackage>
  <DatabaseType>ORACLE</DatabaseType>
  <QueryVersion>V1</QueryVersion>
  <QueryAddedDate>25/05/2020</QueryAddedDate>
  <DataSet>10</DataSet>
  <Description>The following sample SQL query displays the sources, values and filing dates for a specific  company and data item as of a specific period end date.</Description>
</Query></Dataset>
